Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive, 1960-2004 (Bulk 1973-2000) MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence, 173084
  - Subseries A: Individuals, 173085
    - Johnston, Becky, 1982; 173880 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Jordan, John, 1996; 173881 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Josefowicz, Linda (Red Ink Productions), 1974-5; 173882 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - [Josephine], undated; 173883 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Kamm, Peter, 1992; 173885 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Kamper, Dietmar, 1986; 173886 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - [Kamter], Gerard, 1980; 173887 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Kathi, Tod, Gretchen and Ruth, undated; 173888 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Katz, Judith K. (Case Western), 1971; 173889 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Katz, Steve, undated; 173890 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Kelly, Mary, 1991; 173891 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Kelsey, Alison F., 1970; 173892 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Kelsey, John, 1987-2005; 173893 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Kelsey, Louise, 1973; 173894 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Kennison, Don (Amok Press/Paragon House), 1988-9; 173895 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Kent, Thomas, 1988; 173896 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Kierman, Kathy, 1995; 173897 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Kim, undated; 173898 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Kimball, Arthur Samuel, 1985; 173899 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - King, Kenneth, 1977-8; 173900 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - King, Sebastian, 1998; 173901 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Kinser, Sam, 1976-82; 173902 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Kirshenblatt-[Jimblat], Barbara, 1980; 173903 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Kitao, Timothy K., 1969; 173904 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Klaus, Petra, 1988; 173905 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - [Kleen, Judise], 1974; 173906 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - [Koblan, Ken], [1990]; 173907 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - [Kofurau, Sarah], 1988; 173908 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Kolber, Jane, 1979-84; 173909 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Kolosy, Katy, undated; 173910 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Kornacker, David, 1995; 173911 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1995-6; 173912 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Kotz, Liz, 1992; 173913 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris, 1985-2000; 173914 (Box 3, Folder 124)
      Separated Materials
      All materials in this folder returned to donor.
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris- series of letters with Jim, undated; 173915 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Ruth and Oz, 1986-95; 173916 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Krauss, Rosalind, 1986; 173917 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Kretschmer, Sybille, 1986; 173918 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Kristeva, Julia, 1972; 173919 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Kritzman, Larry, 1977; 173920 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Krueger, Imke, 2000; 173921 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Krueger, Marlis, 1981-5; 173922 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Kruger, Hanspeter, 1996; 185578 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Kuhlbrodt, Dietrich, 1981; 173923 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - "La classe", undated; 173924 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Laederach, Jurg, 1984-91; 173925 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Laferriere, Daniel, 1972-3; 173926 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Laing, R. D., 1976-8; 173927 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Laporte, Roger, 1975; 173928 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - [Laselle], Andrea, c. 1989-92; 173929 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Lasser, Danielle, 2006; 173930 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Lasvergnas, Isabelle (UQAM), 2005; 173931 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - "La tua americana", 1983; 173932 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Laurie, c. 1984; 173933 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Lavin, Doug, undated; 173934 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Lazarin, Michael, 1980-92; 173935 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Leach, Neil, 1995; 173936 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Leavis, F.R., 1965; 173937 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Lebel, Jean-Jacques, 1978-2000; 173938 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Lecercle, J.J., 1999; 173939 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - [Le Coedie], Paule, 1979; 173940 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - [Lehmann, John], 1961-4; 173941 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Leigh, Jim, 1988-9; 173942 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Lemaire, Gerard-Georges, 2002; 173943 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Lemelin, Jean-Marc, 1984; 173944 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Leo, Mia, 173945 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - [Leonard, Daniel], undated; 173946 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Lermond, Lucia, [1985]; 173947 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - [Lesal], undated; 173948 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1964; 173951 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Levine, Beverly, 1978; 173949 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Levine, Caren, c. 1993; 173950 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Lewandowski, Matthias, 1986; 173952 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Lewis, Phil (Diacritics), undated; 173953 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Li, Etienne, 1986; 173954 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - [Lia], [1974]; 173955 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Linda, 1978; 173956 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Lindo, Karen U., undated; 173957 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Lipkind, Lynne, 1993; 173958 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Lisa, 1988-90; 173959 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Lischka, Gerhard Johann, 1983-6; 173960 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Liscia, Yolanie, 1958; 173961 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Lisker, Roy, 1979; 173962 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Liza, undated; 173963 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Lizzie, undated; 173964 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - [Loisy, Sydney], c. 1972; 173965 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Lopatin, Judy, 1991; 173966 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Lord, Alan (Ultimatum Magazine), 1986-92; 173967 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Lorentzen, Jorgen, 1983; 173968 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Lorho, Robert, 1960-71; 173969 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - [Loselle, Gilles], 1988; 173970 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Lotringer, M. and Mme (SL's parents), 1956-69; 173971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Lotringer, M. and Mme, 1970-93; 173972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lotringer, M. and Mme, undated; 173973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Lotringer, Lucienne "Bibi" (nee Binet), 1965-74; 173974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Lotringer, Mia (daughter of SL), 1979-2005; 173975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Lotringer, Mia, undated; 173976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere to himself, 1992; 173977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere to unidentified recipients, 1970-90; 173978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Love, Bridget, 1997; 173979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - [Lubgenbonk, Muriel], 1984; 173980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Lucet, Sophie, 1990; 173981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Lucien and Angelique, 1976; 173982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - [Luazin, Fr], 1978-94; 173983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Ludd, Deran, 1990-1; 173984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Ludlow, Janet, 1982; 173985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Lydenberg, Robin, 1987; 173986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Lynda, 1978; 173987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Lynn, 1977; 173988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Lyotard, Jean-Francois, 1976; 173989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "M", 1991; 173990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - [Macaussena, Mr.], 1985; 173991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - McCaffery, Larry, 1992; 173992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - McCarty, V.K., c. 1983-9; 173993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - McGowan, Kate, 1991; 173994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - McGrath, Patrick, 1991-3; 173995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - McKenna, Kristine, undated; 173996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - McKenna, Ross, 1969; 173997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Mackenzie, Michael, 1980; 173998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - McKeon, Roger, 1978-80; 173999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - McMahan, Jane, undated; 174000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - MacMillan, Ian (BBC Television), 1993; 174209 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - McNeill, Linda, undated; 174210 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - [Madne], 1966; 174211 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Mador, Michel, 1978; 174212 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - [Madsen, Virginia], 1988; 174213 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Maija, 1996; 174214 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1986-2002; 174215 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Marazzi, Christian, 1982-99; 174216 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Marcantonio, Francesca, 1991; 174217 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Marcus, Greil, 1983; 174218 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Marcuse, Herbert, 1977; 174219 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Marilyn, 1977-8; 174220 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Marin, Louis, 1976; 174221 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Marion, undated; 174222 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Marjorie, 1970; 174223 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Mark, undated; 174224 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Marlay, Peter (Case Western), 1970; 174225 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Marly, Roger, undated; 174226 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - [Marlene], undated; 174227 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Marlos, Daniel, c. 1994; 174228 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - [Marquarett, Carin], 1984; 174229 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - [Marques, Juanita], undated; 174230 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Marshall, 1989; 174231 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Martel, Richard, 1985-93; 174232 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Martin, Thomas (Basisdruck Verlag), 1997; 174233 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Martini, Oreste, 1985; 174234 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Ma'rton, Koppa'ny, 1984; 174235 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Mary, 1978-9; 174236 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Mary, undated; 174237 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Mary, undated; 174238 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Mary Alice, c. 1983; 174239 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Masson, Monique, 1984-5; 174240 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Masson-Sekine, Nourit, 1990-2; 174241 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Massumi, Brian, 1982-5; 174242 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Mathews, Harry, 1991; 174243 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Matthews, Leroy G. III (Hate mail), 1991; 174244 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Mauron, Charles, 1964-7; 174245 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - [May, L.], 1983; 174246 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Mazlen, Ken, 1978; 174247 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Mehlman, Jeffrey, 1977; 174248 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Mekas, Jonas, 1997; 174249 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Menon, Becca, 1978-90; 174250 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Menzler, Eckart, undated; 174251 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Michel, 1983; 174252 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Michele, 1988; 174253 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - [Mihaff, Marcel], 1991; 174254 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - [Mihok, Michael], 1981; 174255 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Mikriammos, Philippe, 1990; 174256 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Milazzo, Richard, c. 2000; 174257 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - [Miller, Brian], 1992; 174258 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Miller, David, 1998; 174259 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Miller, Hisami Kuroiwa, 1985; 174260 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Miller, Max, 1970; 174261 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Miller, Tony, 1977; 174262 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Millon, Jerome, undated; 174263 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Milstayn, Annick, Gerard and Romain, 1994; 174264 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Milstayn, Yvonne (SL's sister), 1962-79; 174265 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Milstayn, Yvonne, 1981-9; 174266 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Milstayn, Yvonne, 1990-2000; 174267 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Milstayn, Yvonne, undated; 174268 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - [Minier, Sigyn], 1989; 174355 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Minkoff, George Robert, 1990-3; 174356 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - [Mirhej], Andrew, 1984-8; 174357 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Mitchell, Eric, 1977; 174358 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Mitchell, Larry, undated; 174359 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Mitchell, Wanda, 2000; 174360 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - [Miyoshi] (Now Time Magazine}, 1991-3; 174361 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Mladjenovic, Lepa, 1985; 174362 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Monod, Sylvere, 1962; 174363 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Montant, Pierre, 1990; 174364 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Morgan, Robert C., 1988; 174365 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Morganthau, Mr., 1988; 174366 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Morin, France (The New Museum), 1994; 174367 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Morin, Nadia, undated; 174368 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - [Morra, Lois], undated; 174369 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Morris, Mary, 1978-9; 174370 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Morse, Eleanor R., 1971; 174371 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Morton, John, 1994-2004; 174372 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Moshenberg, [Dan], 1987; 174373 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1978; 174374 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Mukherjee, Romi, 1998-9; 174375 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Mulrooney, C., 1993; 174376 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Murray, Alison, 1998; 174377 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - [Mussmann, F.], 1986; 174378 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1984-92; 174379 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Mylle, J.J., undated; 174380 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Naim, Maurice Moshe, 1988; 174381 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - [Nancy], 1988; 174382 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Nancy, Jean-Luc, 1973; 174383 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Nawrot, Daniel, 1969; 174384 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, 1979-93; 174432 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Negri, Toni, 1982-95; 174433 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Neill, Ben, undated; 174434 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Neryo, Edward J., 1996; 174435 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Neuville, Christophe, 1988; 174436 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Nicole, 1970; 174437 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Nicoletti, Mario, 1985; 174438 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Noble, Anne-Solange, 1995; 174439 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - [Noemi], 1977; 174440 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Noguez, Dominique, 1990; 174441 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Noto, John, 1992; 174442 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Oculist, J., 1982; 174443 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Oda, Kaname, 1993; 174444 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - O'Hara, Morgan, 1998; 174445 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Ohayon, Stephane, 1984; 174446 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Olds, Andrew, c. 1989; 174447 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Ollrogge, Birger, 1985; 174448 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Olson, Toby and Miriam, 1987-8; 174449 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Orr, Linda, 1984; 174450 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Ortega, Julio, undated; 174451 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Osborne, Margot, 1989; 174452 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - O'Sullivan, Anna, 1984; 174453 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Ott, Michaela, 1983; 174454 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Ottinger, Ulrike, undated; 174455 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - [Ouivarez], Charlie, 1981; 174456 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Overlie, Mary, 1983; 174457 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Ovid, 1986; 174458 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Palmer, Ron, 2000; 185593 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Paris, Jean, 1969-72; 174459 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - [Parsons, Jay], 1990; 174460 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Pascal, 1979; 174461 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Pat, c. 1983; 174462 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Pearson, Joe, 2000; 174463 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Pelieu, Claude, 1984-6; 174464 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Pell, Derek, 1988; 174465 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Peraldi, Francois (editor of Polysexuality Issue), 1977-86; 174466 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Percy, Henry (Hate mail), 1982; 174467 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Percy, Ingrid, 1999; 185598 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Pericci, Laurie, 1986; 174468 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Perret, Delphine, 1976-85; 174469 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - [Petia], undated; 174470 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Phil, 1977; 174471 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Pichler, Cathrin, 1992-8; 174472 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Pickard-Pritchard, B., 1983; 174473 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Pickens, Richard, 1976-7; 174474 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Piel, Jean, 1970-3; 174475 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Pieniazek, Janine and Steve, 1988; 174476 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Pierssens, Michel (Sub-stance Review), 1971-7; 174477 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Pietkiewicz, Barbara-Mirejlh, 1960-1; 174478 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pimstein, Victor, 1984; 174479 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Piscitelli, Alejandro, 1980; 174480 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Plantenga, Bart, [1986]; 174481 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "POCA", 1982; 174482 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Polizzotit, 1983; 174483 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Pollock, Michele, [1974]; 174484 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pommier, Gerard, 1984; 174485 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - [Ponler], Georges, 1964-6; 174486 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Porter, Doug, 1987; 174487 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Postol, I. Michael, 2000; 174488 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - [Potiche] and Cecile, 1969-70; 174489 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - [Poupon], Pascal, 1981-2; 174490 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1979-80; 174491 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Preston, John, 1983; 174492 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Prigent, Christian, 1978; 174493 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Prigent, Frankie, 1960; 174494 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Pumpkin", 1983; 174495 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Quddus, Marguerite, 1989; 174496 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - "R", 1999; 174497 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Rabi, 1976-2005; 174498 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - [Rabinovici, Shimon], 1962; 174499 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Rabinovitch, Gerard, undated; 174500 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - [Raboniow, Ron], 1971; 174501 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - [Radkewski, Chris], 1981; 174502 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Raggenbass, Rolando, 1986-9; 174503 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - [Raimondi, Sebastien], undated; 174504 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Rapley, Ron, 1999; 174505 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Ratti, Annie, 1984; 174506 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Rattray, David, 1991; 174507 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Rawick, George P., 1980; 174508 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Ray, Nicca (includes ms 'Cherry Bomb'), undated; 174509 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Ray, Nicca, undated; 174510 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ray, Nicca, undated; 174511 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Ready-Made, Blanche, 1993; 174512 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Reale, Egidio, 1988; 174513 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Reeder, Claudia, 1974-5; 174514 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Rehberger, John, undated; 174515 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Reifenberg, Odor Or, 1995; 174516 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Reimers, Ronald (Palimpsest Review), 1982; 174551 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - [Rejuie-Bille, D.], 1975; 174552 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Ren-Lay, Judith, 1992; 174553 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - [Rerret], Elizabeth, undated; 174554 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Rey, [Jean], 1974; 174555 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Ricardou, Jean, 1970-7; 174556 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Richard, 1999; 174557 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Richard, Jean [Curro], [1964]; 174558 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Richard, Pascale, 1984; 174559 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Richards, Gary V., 1980; 174560 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Ridless, Robin, undated; 174573 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Riffaterre, Michael, 1971-98; 174574 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Robbe-Grillet, Catherine, 1980-98; 174575 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Robbins, Joanne, 1979; 174576 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Robert, Alfred, 1994; 174577 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Robert, Marine, 1963; 174578 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Roberts, Mark, 1984; 174579 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Roche, Maurice, 1984-6; 174580 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Rodrigo, Nandi, 1998; 174581 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Rolnick, Suely (also signs as Suely Zolnick), 1986-90; 174582 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Romondino, Annalisa, 1980; 174583 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Ron, undated; 174584 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - [Rosdiansyah], 1995; 174585 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Rosemary, 1981-2; 174586 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - [Rosenbaum, Andy], 1981; 174587 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Rossi, Paul Louis, 1971; 174588 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Rotert, Alfred, 1994; 174589 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - [Rothenberg, Pierre], 1961; 174590 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Rothenberger, Manfred (Bakena), 1990; 174591 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Roubichou, Gerard (Ambassade de France), 1978; 174592 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Roudiez, Leon S. (Chair, Columbia French Dept.), 1971-2; 174626 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Rower, Ann, 1988-93; 174627 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - "RU: anarcho-pacifist", 1987; 174628 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - [Rubin, Jerry], 1983; 174629 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Rukavina, Gregory, 1984; 174630 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Russell, Allan, 1974; 174631 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1961-2; 174632 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Russo, Adelaide, 1974; 174633 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Ruth, undated; 174634 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Rutherford-Dyer, Robert, 1977-86; 174635 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Ryan, 1991; 174874 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Ryan, Paul, 1987; 174875 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - "S", 1983; 174876 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - "S", 1985; 174877 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - "S", undated; 174878 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - "S", undated; 174879 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - "S", undated; 174880 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Sabina, undated; 174881 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Sackville-West, Vita, 1961-2; 174882 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Saenger, Elizabeth, 1986; 174883 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Said, Edward, 1974; 174884 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - [Saint-Amant, Dina], 1995; 174885 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - [Sairita-Jean], Natalie, 1994; 174886 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Salmon, Barbara, 1983-4; 174887 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Sampsell, Kevin (Snipehunt), 1994; 174888 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Sanders, Ed, 1978; 174889 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Sandlin, David, 1997; 174890 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Sarraute, Nathalie, 1963-83; 174891 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Sartorius, Joachim, 1990; 174892 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - [Sayari, Michael], 1980; 174893 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - [Scatt, Zack], undated; 174894 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Scheer, Edward, 1997; 174895 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - [Scheer, S.], 1974; 174896 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Schefer, Jean Louis, 1971; 174897 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Scheff, Janet, 1983-7; 174898 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Schein, Lorraine, undated; 174899 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - [Schickling], Janet, 1984; 174900 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, 1997; 174901 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Schoenbaum, Sam, undated; 174902 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Schoener, Allon, 1985-8; 174903 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Scholder, Amy (City Lights), 1992; 174904 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Schulman, Peter, 1999; 174905 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Schulman, Sarah, 1991; 174906 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Schutze, Bernard, 1987; 174907 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Schwartz, Leonard, 1988; 174908 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Scranton, William, undated; 174909 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Seamus, 2004; 174910 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Seaver, Richard, 1975; 174911 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Seem, Mark, 1975; 174912 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Seglard, Dominique, 1990-9; 174913 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - [Seguret, Eve], 1983; 174914 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - [Sekerci, Bursun], 1969; 174915 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - [Selkow, Bettina], 1984; 174916 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Sellers, Terence, 1982-92; 174917 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Seras, Alexandra, 1983-4; 174918 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Serge, undated; 174919 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - [Seth], 1979; 174920 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Shafir, Yvonne, 1994-5; 174921 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - "Shake", undated; 174922 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - [Shaldeve, Valerie], 1983; 174923 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Shapazian, Robert (Lapis Press), 1986-7; 174924 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Sherman, Stuart, 1980-91; 174925 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Sherpa, Laure, 1982-5; 174926 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Shiba, Shunichi, 1985; 174927 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Shirley, 1970; 174928 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Sidelsky, Monique "Nitza", 1957-99; 174929 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - [Sievernine], Lilyan, 1994; 174931 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 1991; 174930 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Silverman, Michael, 1986; 174932 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Simon, undated; 174933 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Simon, Claude, 1972-83; 174934 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Simon, Isabelle, 1985; 174935 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Simons, Martin, [1985]; 174936 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Sitwell, Osbert, 1961; 174937 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Sivadon-Sabourin, Danielle, 1992-9; 174943 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - [Sksanlik, Myriam], [1986]; 174944 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Skwazczewska, Alicja, 1960; 174945 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Slater, Howard, c. 1995; 174946 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Sloly, Matthew, 1998; 174947 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Smith, Duncan, 1980-6; 174948 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Sontag, Susan, [1997]; 174949 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - [Sorguz], 1969; 174950 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Sotenberg, Marechal des Logis, 1957-8; 174951 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - [Spald], undated; 174952 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Spanos, William V. (Boundary 2), 1973; 174953 (Box 5, Folder 155)